

# STEPHAN ULLRICH

# FULL STACK | BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER

#### **About Me**

Passionate and highly-skilled Full-Stack & Blockchain developer who loves the Pro-gramming.

Over 8 years of experience in the IT field developing full-tested, well-structured, conti-nuously maintainable apps.

With a strong attention to detail and accuracy and the important ability to corporate well in a team work. I will always provide you the perfect result that you want.

#### **Personal Details**

Nationality
Singapore
Marital Status
Single

## Contact

T: +(1)980-270-6138 E: codedev0713@gmail.com

### Website & Social Links

Website

portfolio-62c9b.web.app/

LinkedIn

stephanullrich-26ab8b257

**Telegram** 

@super\_meme\_dev

Discord

funny#6657

Github

star0713

# Language

English: fluent

# Work Ethic

- Honest and hard-working attitude on every projects and services
- Agile/Scrum methodlogy and take best app design patterns/practices
- Hight proficiency in verbal and and written English, daily communicator
- Do the best to meet client's expectation and needs
- Always passionate to learn the most up to date technologies and learn fast
- Devoteing full time and extra service for long-term clients

## Education

# Nanyang Technological University

Bachelor Of Engineering -BE (Computer Science) 2011 - 2015 Singapore, singapore

# Experience

#### SLAMCOIN.IO

11/2021 -09/2022

freelancer

#### Full Stack & Blockchain Developer

(United Arab Emirates)

- Contributed to develop Slam NFT Smart contract and Marketplace Contract on BSC chain.
- Developed Backend with Laravel and Frontend UI with React.js
- Integrated Marketplace site with Smart contract.

Technical stacks:

Solidity (ERC-721, ERC20, ERC-721a), Web3.js, React.js, Tailwind CSS, Laravel, Mysql, AWS(Lambda, S3, SNS)

#### **AlphaX**

10/2019 - 07/2021 full-time

Full Stack & Blockchain Developer

#### **Skills**

Blockchain

Solidity/Rust ERC20/ERC-721/ERC-1155 web3/Ethers.js/Metamask Hardhat/Truffle

Backend

Node.js/Express.js/Nest.js PHP/Laravel/CI Golang/C#/Python

Frontend

React.js/Redux.js Next.js/Nuxt.js Vue.js/Vuetify/Vuex TypeScript/JavaScript HTML5/CSS3/SCSS/SASS

Database

MySql/MongoDB/PostgreSql

☐ Tools

Firebase AWS Git/BitBucket Jira/Trello

#### FEED BACK

Sean - CEO of Self Opportunity

Stephan Ullrich was great to work with We worked for a long time and he was a very dedicated and experienced developer.
There was nothing that he couldn't do: We really appreciate him. He finished all projects before he left the company.
We hope to work with him again soon

- Created Trading Platform that runs on Polygon network
- Used Chain link Data Feed for settle order with real time price
- Implemented the update reward for traders and stakers in solidity with difficulty adjustment algorithm
- Created the crypto currency chart using CoinBase and Binance API Technical stacks:

Solidity (ERC-721, ERC20, ERC-721a), Web3.js, React.js, Tailwind CSS, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, AWS(Lambda, S3, SNS),

#### **Self Opportunity**

05/2017 - 08/2019

full-time

#### **Full Stack Developer**

(Lewisiville, Texas)

Built +10 various websites like Ecommerce, Social Dating, Productivity, Real Estate, Education businesses for 10 to 15 individual clients and startups. Fluent in various programming languages, frameworks, and libraries and have vast experience with them. By working with some development teams and clients remotely, I have been skilled in communications for remote working and teamwork cooperation. Normally use Slack for communications and use Jira for developments.

#### Technical stacks:

PHP, Laravel, React.js, Vue.js, Typescript, Redux, Node.js, Express.js, Python, C#, MongoDB, MySql, Firebase, React-Native, AWS, Tailwind CSS, BootStrap

#### **SOFTIQ**

04/2015 - 08/2017

freelancer

#### **Full Stack Developer**

I have built many websites and mobile applications like Live Chatting Fitness App, Dating Website and Mobile App, Shopping and Booking s using Angular, React, Node, Laravel, MongoDB, React Native, IONIC Collaborated with other developers to identify and alleviate so ware errors and inefficiencies.

09/2013 - 01/2015

freelancer

#### Junior Full Stack Developer

Collaborated in a cross-functional team of 5 interns on the company. We learned how to use git and another frontend technical stacks.